<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PoemEBook</string>
    <string name="moonlit">In the heart of night under moon\'s gentle gaze, Whispers of mischief in the forest\'s embrace.
        \nShadows dance lightly on a silvery floor,\n Secrets and stories of the night\'s ancient lore.\n Tiny feet patter in a joyful parade,\n Under the watch of the ever-watchful glade.\n Moonlit beams catch on wings, a fleeting kiss,\n In this moment, time holds only bliss.\n Creatures of night, in their playful quest, \n Find in each shadow a place to jest.\n The forest alive with laughter and glee,\n A magical world only they can see.\n In the gleam of the moon, mysteries unfold,\n Tales of the night, bravely bold.\n Mischief and wonder in every glance,\n In the woodland\'s embrace, they dance.\n So when the moon ascends the sky\'s grand stage,\n And night cloaks the world in its wise, old age,\n Remember the magic that thrives unseen,\n In the heart of the forest, where the night has been.\n</string>
    <string name="butterfly">In a meadow bathed in sunlight\'s glow,\n Butterflies whisper to flowers below.\n Secrets carried on gentle breeze,\n In a dance as old as the trees.\n \n Wings of color, a silent flutter,\n Messages in each beat they utter.\n To the blooms that eagerly listen,\n In their petals, dewdrops glisten.\n \n A world of wonder, small and grand,\n Where nature\'s beauty is close at hand.\n Each butterfly, a fleeting dream,\n In this serene, sunlit stream.\n \n So listen close and you might hear,\n The softest whispers, crystal clear.\n In the heart of nature\'s embrace,\n Butterfly whispers fill the space.\n</string>
    <string name="puddle">In a world washed anew by rain\'s embrace,\n Children laugh, in puddles they race.\n Rubber boots splash, a joyous sound,\n In every leap, freedom is found.\n \n Rainbow reflections in water\'s mirror,\n Moments of magic, ever dearer.\n A chorus of droplets, a rhythmic ballet,\n In every splash, they dance away.\n \n The storm recedes, but joy remains, In every puddle, happiness reigns.\n So let the skies pour down their tale, Of children and puddles, love that prevails.</string>
    <string name="secret">Beneath the velvet cloak of night,\n Where stars whisper secrets of ancient light.\n Children gaze, wide-eyed and bright,\n At tales untold in the celestial height.\n \n A campfire\'s glow, soft and warm,\n Illuminates faces in the night\'s charm.\n Each constellation, a mythical form,\n Holds a story, a storm, a stellar swarm.\n \n In this moment, time seems to pause,\n Captivated by the universe\'s laws.\n The sky, a canvas without flaws,\n Invites the soul to ponder, to explore its cause.\n \n The secret life of stars, a mystery profound,\n In their silence, the cosmos\' heartbeat is found.\n In awe, we stand on this hallowed ground,\n Where the whispers of eternity abound.\n</string>
    <string name="dragon">In a realm where dragonflies dance and gleam,\n Above a pond, a mirror to the sky\'s dream.\n Iridescent wings flutter in radiant beams,\n Weaving through sunlight, a liquid stream.\n \n Their flight, a ballet of grace and speed,\n Over waters where whispered secrets breed.\n In this enchanting world, they lead,\n A dance of joy, where no heart can bleed.\n \n Colors blend, in the air and below,\n Reflecting the hues of the rainbow\'s glow.\n Dragonfly dreams, where time moves slow,\n In the dance of life, they come and go.\n \n Here, in the embrace of nature\'s calm,\n Peace resides, a healing balm.\n In the flight of the dragonfly, a psalm,\n A reminder of the world\'s serene palm.\n</string>
    <string name="squirrel">In the heart of the forest, where whispers tell,\n A sneaky squirrel stashes away its spell.\n Beneath the canopy of autumn\'s flame,\n Hiding acorns, in a never-ending game.\n \n With a flick of its tail, swift and sly,\n It scurries about, under the watchful sky.\n Leaves rustle with each clever dash,\n Secret spots for its winter cache.\n \n Around it, the forest sings in hues of gold,\n A tale of preparation, bold and old.\n Each buried treasure, a story untold,\n Of survival and cunning, in the cold.\n \n So, watch closely where the leaves may fall,\n For the sneaky squirrel is the master of all.\n In the dance of seasons, it plays its part,\n With each acorn, a piece of the forest\'s heart.\n</string>
    <string name="frog">As dusk enfolds the woodland\'s lush embrace,\n Frogs gather at the pond, their sacred space.\n A symphony begins, as if on cue,\n In twilight\'s glow, their world anew.\n Each croak a note, the air vibrates,\n A melody that the night creates.\n The pond, a stage for this chorus grand,\n A natural wonder, unplanned, yet planned.\n The setting sun, with lingering light,\n Bathes the scene in hues so bright.\n Silhouettes of leaves, and ripples on water,\n In this concert, nature\'s sons and daughters.\n As stars peek through the veil of night,\n The frogs\' song continues, pure delight.\n In every note, life\'s simple plea,\n For harmony, joy, and the freedom to be.\n</string>
    <string name="rainbow">After the storm has had its say,\n And clouds gently part, making way.\n A ribbon of colors, bold and bright,\n Stretches across the sky, light after night.\n \n From earth to heavens, it arcs so high,\n Painting hope across the somber sky.\n A promise of peace, a fresh start,\n A bridge from shadow to sunny heart.\n \n Each hue a whisper of dreams to come,\n Of laughter, joy, and then some.\n In every drop of rain that falls,\n A rainbow waits, to all it calls.\n \n So let the storms come, let them go,\n For after rain, rainbows show.\n A reminder, in every droplet\'s gleam,\n After hardship, comes the dream.\n</string>
    <string name="whale">In the depths where silent stories dwell,\n Whales sing their songs, a deep-sea spell.\n Majestic beings in the ocean\'s embrace,\n Moving through water, with effortless grace.\n \n Their melodies travel, a haunting call,\n Through liquid vastness, an echo to all.\n A language of giants, so ancient and deep,\n Whispers of mysteries the ocean does keep.\n \n Beneath the surface, where light fades to blue,\n Their songs weave a magic, both old and new.\n A symphony born from the heart of the sea,\n Telling tales of what was, and what will be.\n \n In each note, a story of endless wander,\n Of depths uncharted, where one can ponder.\n The wonders of a world hidden from sight,\n Revealed in the song of the whale\'s night.\n</string>
    <string name="garden">In a hidden nook where laughter blooms,\n A garden thrives, dispelling glooms.\n Where every flower chuckles in the breeze,\n And trees tell jokes to the busy bees.\n \n Sunlight dances on leaves so green,\n In this haven, joy is keen.\n Giggles float on the air, so light,\n Filling hearts with pure delight.\n \n Fairies giggle as they flit around,\n Their laughter, a melodious sound.\n Animals chatter in playful banter,\n In this garden, happiness is the anchor.\n \n A magical place where smiles grow free,\n And happiness blooms for you and me.\n The Garden of Giggle, a rare find,\n Where laughter leaves no one behind.\n</string>
</resources>